FERNANDA NAUATA Front-End Developer

Portfolio fernandanauata.com

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/fernanda-nauata

E-mail contact@alvesfernanda.com

Skype alves.fernanda2

GitHub github.com/fernandanauata

Phone 778.891.4854

I have solid working knowledge with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap, and I am currently learning Javascript MV* Frameworks (i.e. Backbone.js, AngularJS and Knockout) and Jasmine javascript testing framework. In addition, I have 5+ years of experience as a Graphic Designer and have mastered Adobe Softwares (i.e. Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects).

O O O O O O O O TECHNICAL SKILLS

WEB SKILLS: CSS, HTML, web standards and accessibility, JavaScript, mobile web designs, MV* Framework, jQuery, Bootstrap, UI/UX Design

APPLICATION SOFTWARE: Adobe Acrobat, Adobe Creative Suite (i.e. Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects), Sketch, Balsamiq

OPERATING SYSTEMS: Windows, MAC OS

EDUCATION

UDACITY

September - December 2016

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER NANODEGREE

Learn how to make beautiful, responsive websites optimised for mobile and desktop performance. Get deep in how the web works and gain a working knowledge of the three foundational languages that power websites: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

RED ACADEMY Canada | October - December 2016

PART-TIME PROGRAMS, WEB DEVELOPER FOUNDATION

The Web Developer Foundation is a comprehensive part time Certificate program, designed to give a solid foundation in the principles of Web Development. The course is designed to teach the skills, tools and software being used in today's industry.

ESTÁCIO DE SÁ Brazil | July 2009 - June 2013

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, ADVERTISING AND MARKETING

.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INSUITS MARKETING Canada | October 2016 - Present

WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Develop mock-ups and prototypes to effectively communicate interaction and design ideas
- Promote quality and consistent User Interface and User Experience design
- Work on a variety of outputs from web design to print (i.e. Social Media images, brochures, web sites and more)

MKT BRASIL

Brazil | January 2013 - June 2014

ART DIRECTOR

- Develop the overall visual aspects of advertising campaigns
- · Work with the team to create concept and design elements, such as colors and photographs.
- · Work on short-run design projects such as stationery, business cards, brochures, email invitations
- Talked with clients to receive their feedback and perform any tweaks for ensuring a high quality of the piece before sending it for printing.

DOZE

Brazil | September - November 2012

ART DIRECTOR

- Set the concept for design projects such as stationery, business cards, brochures, email invitations
- Ensure the quality of the files for printing.

MIDIANOVA Brazil | January - October 2012

GRAPHIC DESIGNER JUNIOR

- Assist the Art Directors to print files in the correct format and resolution
- After a while I was given more interesting tasks as creating graphic elements where I could show my
 imagination. (i. e. I designed stationery, business cards, in-house brochures, email invitations and
 print ads.)